Next, let's look at the second case.
In this case, we see a set of tight underwear, tight pants, and a leather jacket.
When there is a tight structure inside, it is the same.
For the waist, we need to apply some stretch marks.
After applying stretch marks, we can prevent it from deforming.
After selecting the pattern, find the stretch marks in the attribute editor.
Click to select.
After selecting, you can select some suitable stretch marks in the preset stretch marks attribute.
Here I use common.
Using stretch marks will make it difficult to stretch.
Not easy to stretch means that after some large-scale movements,
it is not easy to deform.
So we will use stretch marks in some key parts,
such as the bottom of the shirt or the waist of the pants.
In this case, changing the fabric of the waist belt to Fusible Rigid
and stretching for the waist belt application is the same effect.
So in the first episode, we saw that it is also possible to change the fabric of the waist belt to Fusible Rigid.
Open the animation editor at the bottom of the screen.
By dragging the progress bar, we will see that the movement speed of this action is relatively low.
So we need to fix some key parts of this set of clothes.
Now let's go back to the first frame.
In the first frame, we first hide the outer layer of the clothes.
Here we can see that due to the transformation of the morph target just now,
it may lead to the problem of our shoulder belt slipping.
If we record animation afterwards, it will also slip.
So here we use the function of fixing to the virtual model.
So we first select the outer layer of the jacket and press Shift-Q.
We can hide some of these sheets.
At the same time as hiding the sheets, open the simulation, drag the shoulder belt to the appropriate position.
After stopping the simulation, we can switch to the function of fixing to the virtual model.
Click on the sheet and click on the virtual model.
Fix the position of the sheet on the virtual model.
After adjusting this side, we will adjust the other side.
Make sure that the point between the two points is not too far away when adding the virtual model.
When adding the virtual model, make sure that the two points are not too far away.
After adding the virtual model, we can display all the sheets.
Let's go to the model.
All the panels can be displayed by pressing Shift W.
Here, because the chest of the virtual model is relatively large,
sometimes due to some stretching problems,
the panel of the chest is deformed.
Here we select this panel line of the repair panel.
Open the flexible in the right mouse button editor
and set the flexible ratio to 100.
After setting to 100, this edge will no longer deform.
When you start the simulation, it will slowly return to
what it looks like in the 2D version.
This way, we can effectively prevent some parts
from deforming due to intense stretching or movement.
After we pull it in, we can see that
because it is now added to the flexible,
the position of the collar here looks a bit out of place.
We can use the editor's sewing function
to move the point on the virtual model,
making this curve look more face-sensitive and more round.
The next thing we need to fix is the button.
Here we can see that
because this pair of pants is a tight pair of pants,
because its waist is now only maintained by a button and a buttonhole,
if the movement is large, the buttonhole is easy to pierce.
In order to prevent the subsequent buttonhole from being unstable,
we need to re-create the structure of its waist here.
Here, we first use the move button tool to move the button.
To move the button, we use the button to move the button.
Move the button to the position near the front of the waist.
Because we will create an inner line here later,
this inner line will be sewed together later.
So don't let the inner line and the button have a reunion.
Then we use the inner multidirectional line tool
to create an inner line,
then press Ctrl C, Ctrl R to put it next to it.
After creating the inner line,
we need to create a sewing line on the inner line and the outer line of the board.
We need to create a sewing line on the inner line and the outer line of the board.
Then take the sewing line and secure it.
After it is fixed, we can start the simulation.
Let them calculate for a while,
and we can start adjusting the button.
I will turn off the interruption of the button here.
In general, the button interruption is randomly started.
If the interruption was started,
Let's take a look at it here, it may be a little unstable sometimes
For example, when we move the board, we will see that this button will have some kind of floating feeling in the air
If we turn off the conflict here, it will not have this problem
Next is about the pocket part
Because here, my pocket production method does not actually merge it into the inner layer to make the actual pocket effect
Sometimes when we make such a pocket part, we may make it into a fake pocket cloth and stick it inside
If there is compression in the process of movement, it may be compressed from the inside to the outside
Let's record it first to see if there will be such a problem in the middle
Here we set the simulation quality to 5 as before
Then the scene change time is also set to 5
In the process of recording, press Alt 3 to switch to the black and white surface
So we can go more directly to see if there is a problem with the board
In the process of recording, we will see that the pocket here will fall out
So we now need to make some adjustments to the pocket
But in the process of adjustment, we cannot adjust it in the current frame
Because once we start to make some adjustments to the grid, this action bar will disappear
Because it is a grid
And the information is no longer usable
So we have to go back to the first frame and make further adjustments
First, we click on the start and go back to the first frame
After going back to the first frame, we can start to adjust the board
Here I adjust the board, you will see that the animation file in our animation column will disappear
Because the costume file has now been changed
After that, we may need to start recording again from the beginning
Here we press I to switch to the collocation outline tool
Then select the edge of this pocket part
Right-click to select the inner shape
Then this edge will be automatically collocated into the inner line
We can switch to the editor board tool
Select this line, Ctrl C, Ctrl V, copy and paste to our pocket board
Then align its inner line
After choosing the inner line, find this inner dot in the menu
Then move it to the two corners of the board outline line
After moving the end point of the inner line, we can start cutting
Before we delete the extra inner line on the pants
If you don't delete it, there may be a problem with the sewing line later
Because if the outer and inner lines of the board overlap, the sewing line may be mistaken
Then we select this extra pocket board and delete it with the Delete key
Then we put it on both sides and sew it together here
After the pocket is sewn together, we can start to cut it out
Don't forget that because we changed the pocket board first
Then the sides also have to be sewed together with free sewing
After sewing, I saw that there may be some penetrations in the process of simulation
So we first reduce the particle diameter and then simulate
Here we choose the pants board
Reduce the particle diameter to 8
And we manipulate the pattern more
In this way, the pattern of the pants occupation is completed
Then press the permanently off key to simulate
Finally, we press Alt 1 to switch back to the thicker texture surface
Then you can start recording again
Finally, let's take a look at the project of the bag
You can see that it space processing is very fast
The picture looks like this
Next, we take out the next piece
You can see that the pattern of the pocket board is like this
You can see that the pattern is completely different
You can see that there is actually no more unstable place
Because now they are integrated into a whole version